because if you have kids you have to
love them all unconditionally as an
uncle you pick your favorite so I'm
coming off a great Christmas if anyone's
from a big family you might have the
system we have we don't get every
sibling this egg if we pick one name
give one sibling a gift and it worked
out perfect
last winter I picked my oldest brother
and I asked you what he thinks a good
present for someone who owes you money I
got him a gift certificate to me
[Laughter]
I felt real good go there you go mark
remember that 400 you owe me it's down
to 380 happy holidays I love the
holidays though I love anything with a
little kid so he's always like now I've
only been a father for two Christmases
but I've been an uncle for a long time
that's a sweet gig too that's that's
might tell a lot of young people I go
don't let anyone pressure you to have
children you should pressure your
siblings to make something because you
can't beat an or uncles the greatest
right cuz cuz if you have kids you have
to love them all unconditionally as an
uncle we pick your favorite
[Applause]
okay that's part of Christmas how come
you didn't get a Christmas present
because you're hard to be around that's
why you didn't get a gram
[Applause]
no I'm not cheap i buy your sister a
pony look in the back guy got her a pony
I don't think you guys get behind that
one all right hello there's a little
meaner than I thought here in Utah hey
know what holidays really changed in my
lifetime culturally Easter because my
nieces and nephews it they opened prep
these kids expect presents for Easter of
all times to change me when I was a kid
my father didn't even cover the Easter
eggs he just bought brown eggs and he
hid them in the same spot every year
behind the mayonnaise in the fridge if
you found them good make me an omelet
okay I gotcha pop so my wife is Jewish
from people I don't you know people
that's not is yeah I think you should be
a bigger deal people don't care as much
I get this question was about people
your wife's choocha is she real
religious no uh apparently not married
me in fact I'm a better true than her I
married a Jew and she can't say that
[Applause]
okay then I made two more Jews up for an
Irish kid okay that's pretty impressive
there's a mediocre Catholic now I'm a
good Jew it's pretty exciting I gotta be
honest with what people do tell me with
with my daughter's sake oh you're not a
you know your daughters are Jewish but
of course they have to us to go no no no
they're all Jewish well that's pretty
cool you don't when they get older
people can ask their heritage what am i
all Jewish plus half Irish I'll be great
on job interviews you need someone I
give 150% you're looking at it right
here this is my first time here this is
very scenic place I grew up in Syracuse
New York that's the snowiest city in the
whole country and they don't even
acknowledge it I remember as a kid see
in an ice-cream truck with a snowplow
blade come down this street go ahead now
I assume most people are from the Provo
area but we might have some out-of-town
guests my advice when you travel no
matter where you go don't tell the
locals what you're doing because no
matter what they're like that stuff's
all touristy
oh I'm a tourist you want me to get a
job this week what that banking better
get back to work all sunburned people
hey where'd you go to the Caribbean no I
ended up roofing in Florida this is a
beautiful town and went to up to the
campus and took some photos you got the
dramatic mountains in the back are some
believable then he ever sent someone a
photo that's his cell phone cameras
don't capture that he sent it to someone
else so what do you look what Golf and
where are you the real thing right there
so good to be with this hotel by myself
I'm a married man we have some married
folks here I'm sure huh
[Applause]
I just got married four years ago a
little late that was an older older
groom I'm glad I waited because you know
guys in their 20s are very shallow they
just care about looks but as you mature
you look for a soul mate with money I
[Applause]
was always hoping to meet a woman with a
raspy voice that's very attractive to
men men we hear a woman with a raspy
voice we think hey maybe she's all done
yelling anyone engaged in the room but
we have some young love anyone engaged
no I like meeting the engaged people
because I feel like I have wisdom
finally because by the time I got
married my friends were all married and
they gave me a great tip they go hey
when you playing the wedding whatever
you order if the vendors find out it's
for a wedding they raised their prices
oh okay so we were sly we went to the
bakery together we hey we need a three
layer cake with a formal couple on top
for a fundraiser our friends got injured
ballroom dancing
then he got a reserved hotel rooms way
in advance if you have out-of-town
friends so my wife handle that you call
it the hotel goes hi yeah we need to
reserve a dozen hotel rooms for next
November of next year and we're hoping
to get a discount because it's for a
funeral things are good things are good
at home one source of tension I married
a morning person my wife is a relentless
morning person she'll wake me up to tell
me I can keep sleeping
[Laughter]
hey it's six o'clock but you can sleep
till 7:00 I know you told me at 5:00
[Applause]
she says I sleep too much she said
that's a sign of depression oh yeah but
I was happy when I was sleeping but
neither one of us are sleeping as much
anymore but for happy reasons coz two
years ago we had a beautiful baby girl
how about that probe Oh huh we named her
cheap applause that's my daughter's name
then a year ago we had daughter number
two we named her standing ovation
everybody know that that is true I got
two beautiful girls at home kids are
great moms a little colicky but the kids
are doing great parents might round
applause I'm sure we got a lot of
parents here
[Applause]
most you're probably way ahead of me and
you probably gonna laugh but I think
it's kidding I don't want to jinx it I
feel like it's getting less difficult I
felt like the newborn stage and my
limited experience is the most
challenging but newborns are tough right
come home from the hospital all wiped
out then all your friends want to come
over they're all good intention there
hey we want to see the baby when's the
best time to see the baby 4:00 a.m.
would be real helpful
don't be late we're leaving her by the
door for you
I love being a parent though there's a
big perk I wish I knew about this when I
was a younger man the coolest thing is
as soon as you have a child from that
moment on you get to pretend that your
opinion has more merit on every topic no
matter what people are talking about
listen to hey hey as a father
of two little girls why would you throw
a pass from the one-yard line
[Laughter]
[Applause]
my wife has a real job in case you're
nervous for us I know whenever a
comedian says he has kids the crowds
like what do you feed him punchlines
how's that what now my wife's got a good
job I don't know what she does but we
got HBO Showtime Cinemax
yes p.m. know my wife's lying to work to
digital marketing which I knew nothing
about I still know but I don't know much
about it but basically she's got social
media for big companies so if you want
to be Facebook friends with your
toothpaste my wife can hook that up so
she's got a me on all the social media I
feel I'm a little old for that but she's
got me on social media so I'm on Twitter
but my wife don't want to pay attention
me so I just tweet did you feed the dog
hashtag he looks hungry get a hungry
looking dog so we're from slightly
different backgrounds I grew up in
upstate anywhere and grew up in Syracuse
New York like I said big family and I
got three brothers three sisters and my
father's warming up to us now which is
exciting you know
growing up well we were all in the house
we drove my dad crazy you know he seven
kids in the house he didn't hide it
either we used to go on those field
trips in school we give our dad the
permission slip it's got that question
in case of an emergency my dad right do
not resuscitate
but now he's all sentimental so now and
the whole family gets together my father
gets his camcorder out I still got the
camcorder right and I'll record
everybody right and then he's so excited
he'll play the tape right then and to be
polite we sit down to watch it you ever
been to a party where the second half of
the party you're forced to watch video
of the first half his memory lane right
here dad boy those were the today's my
father is a former Marine any military
in the room former military in Roubaix
Rana Plaza there we go good guys Debbie
oh yeah now if there's any Marines here
they're gonna be unhappy with how I
phrase it they say my father is a former
Marine marine said there's no such thing
once a marine always a marine and I love
that sentiment but it leads to a lot of
disappointment if I tell people hey my
father's a Marine they go whoa where is
he stationed I go he's stationed at a
kitchen table and Syracuse play art he's
currently defending his crossword puzzle
from my mom operation keep the pencil
now my wife's an only child she's from
New York City but then I live in New
York City now I moved to New York City I
moved there cuz that City has so much
energy and then I learned the city gets
its energy by sucking it out of the
people that live there then my friends
visit me and they go hey what's your
favorite thing to do in New York City I
find parking really that's the most
exciting sometimes finding a parking
spot it's so exciting I pull out and
look for another one to get that rush
again you know I got it
it's like my catch-and-release so my
wife's from New York City and she's an
only child
so early in our courtship she was very
interested in the logistics of a large
family and she would ask me school all
right when your whole family gets
together who cooks Mahon here's the
situation my parents are both Irish and
Irish parents have a lot of kids and
then they pray that one of them marries
an Italian Irish meal plan right there
that is true that is true my sister
married an Italian guy he's first
generation he cooks more for dinner
every night that I saw K through six is
unbelievable Oh Gerry where are we in
the 1970s I was packaged for a whole
decade I could've used it could have
used you so but my wife I thought she
was Irish I met my wife on the Internet
how about that eight years ago we met on
the internet and I'm amazed were still
together because she returns everything
she gets online
[Applause]
I'm glad you like that job so we that's
sure we met eight years ago now we
didn't know what to tell our parents
about the internet date it's a little
weird for me it's like a generational
thing you know we told our parents so we
met at the University of Phoenix but I
thought you guys I Rashmi so name is
Molly my wife's name is Molly sounds
Irish but she's not ours little
curveball I don't think we're gonna have
anyone in the room my wife is a choice
we have a Jewish friends here in Provo
it's Roseanne Barr in the room did you
come back to Utah
she's the only Jewish person to Utah get
bigger now my neighborhood we didn't
have any Jewish families where I grew up
too so I don't know anything about the
Jewish culture but I'm learning and I
find with any religion or culture
there's more similarities than there are
differences there's a Jewish holiday Yom
Kippur I've never asked my life I go how
did Jewish people celebrate Yom Kippur
and she says we don't eat I go that's
identical to a holiday my culture st.
Patrick's Day
[Laughter]
all right
but then she educated me turns out
that's a serious holiday I apologize
what's the most festive Jewish holiday
my wife said Christmas Chinese food and
go to the movies like Christmas yeah so
things are good at home things were real
good at home me my what you don't we
pick about picking a restaurant my wife
I love it's cuz she's from Manhattan
there's so many you know she always
asked me what i watch cuz what do you
want to eat I go uh let's get some Thai
food here's my wife no I can't
I can't have Thai food today I had Thai
food yesterday no people in Thailand
handle that pretty well you know
now the food inside the house is getting
a little more exotic - we don't have
rice sushi banish'd raised replaced it
with quinoa yeah she died what's at the
grocery store she texted me to get so
I'm asking yeah what I always put Noah
yeah where do I find it
quinoa I know if everyone's had quinoa
quinoa is good quinoa is good if you put
it in something that was already good no
one's ever been eating some random dish
of food going to there's a little bland
I think a little quinoa would bring it
out you know so everything of my wife's
in charge of the food everything's
organic - we have organic peanut butter
does anyone in the room have a beagle I
have a theory even a beagle won't eat
organic peanut butter stuff stuff man if
you've never had organic peanut butter
you can make it yourself you don't need
to go buy it here's how you make organic
peanut but just get out your regular
peanut butter and then pour oil on top
of it and then somehow remove all the
peanut butter flavor I don't know how to
well here's the final step this is
crucial the final step take a $20 bill
and drop that in the garbage
my wife's getting a little crazy where
there died I'm getting worried about she
gets on the internet she's always
looking for the next trend you know but
she doesn't challenge anything here's
what you told me one time she goes hey
we're not supposed to be drinking milk
as adults because were the only species
that does it I know hon we're the only
species that can milk cows that's part
of the puzzle
squirrels would love to have some
icecream from time to time
but they're undisciplined
milk Bobby it's got my back right there
there we go
[Music]
sometimes I have to show us people hey
you know we take a lot of swipes at your
wife during your set and she's not here
to defend herself I know yeah this what
we call best case scenario everybody is
I'm pretty brave
what am out of town
but she's always on me for something 3q
don't use hounding me for I liked it
last year for the whole year so I mean
to grow a beard because you should grow
a beard I don't want to come you should
definitely what's it a little backhanded
now you can compliment a gentleman on
his existing beard but tell someone no
beard to get one I know what you saying
what she was really saying was that hey
you know what could help your face less
of it
[Applause]
swept in 4k everybody 4k are a lot of
pixels going on right now guys are fun
good so what else is going on we live in
crazy times hope everyone's having a
good year and everything now if you're
one I don't do political so I don't
really do political jokes you know why
because when comedians begin they always
tell us like oh don't don't do political
jokes because only 50% of the crowd is
gonna like your joke right but then you
do comedy long enough in here like hey
50 percents not that bad for one of my
pretty good but it's not 50% cuz 50%
don't even vote say I want to hear you
then you're splitting again now you're
down to 25% the hello it's a little
risky hey by the way they just came out
finally nationwide with for the people
who don't vote they've come out with
early not voting so you don't have to
wait till Election Day not to vote
yeah like a month the four weeks before
the election you go down to the Board of
Elections oh how you doing
yeah I'm not voting you need photo ID
though they're very strict they're very
strict because there's been not voting
fraud where people are not voting in
more than one district you know but here
is a one innocuous bipartisan political
joke so we all follow the election and
it comes down to the swing states they
make it too complicated basically if you
win Ohio and Florida you will be the
president right so I'm telling you right
now a future president is LeBron James
everybody that comes he's got Ohio
wrapped up right and he won two titles
in Florida but maybe if he needs help
with the older voters his running mate
Jimmy Buffett done deal right there
here's a bumper sticker that King James
Buffet right there to get you I'm a big
sports fan more than anything I love
sports we got some Cougars fans in the
room mary-elizabeth doesn't name my high
school so I'm gonna tell myself you're
cheering for my high school we're all
happy here
this guy like Cougars good name I don't
like my team shirt Tigers right because
hey we don't have Tigers in North
America that no Tigers if we gonna be
named after an animal it should be
indigenous and really half the teams in
the country should be the deer everyone
should just be the deer a lot of deer
I'd be a great mascot to halftime in the
basketball game to people in the deer
costume
and go out the center court I don't know
where a Ford 150 truck boom
but here's the inspirational Martha then
dear get up and run away
and the truck the truck has $3,000
front-end collision damage and the deer
win by 20 so I'm a big sports fan
they beat swear we've had some good
events lately we had a good good
Superbowl very dramatic I'm big football
I played football in college I don't
know if you know that it's outside
I played foosball and God
[Laughter]
we had a great World Series last year
now I'm not from Chicago but Mandy can't
beat that for drama in the Cubs they had
one in a hundred and eight years they
get the World Series it goes Game seven
extra innings and they went in a hole I
ran outside and flipped over my own car
seemed like the right thing to do yeah I
always watch the world sir I love the
World Series regular season a little
slow you know I never know to a game any
sport they hire an organ player to spike
up the action with an organ player
like the team owners out there I'm
worried if we got some walls hey my
uncle plays organ we'll get in there
he knows everything little bit today he
knows that one nobody closes with dental
baseball's got the weirdest legal
problems - like the two biggest players
of my generation Barry Bonds Roger
Clemens
they both had perjury trials right now I
don't know anything about the law but I
bet we do have some legal lines in the
room
my understanding of perjury trials where
they go hey you're on trial because last
time you're on trial you lied to us is
that true so I like a lot of sports that
aren't as poppy I'm a tennis fan I don't
know if there's any of us left about it
beautiful sport tennis here's how they
can attract more viewers they got to get
rid of the ball boys and the ball girls
and replace them with golden retrievers
everybody loves gold this golden club
tennis balls win-win-win the chair
umpire dipped it drop it good boy
good boy so what else said now I'm a big
Olympics fan now well here we had some
Winter Olympics excitement here right in
there in this town yeah not the Winter
Olympics they're coming up the Winter
Olympics they're in Korea
hopefully South Korea have we
double-checked on that oh ho but I get
well I always get I get wound up for the
Winter Games cuz I'm from the snow belt
and then but they got it they got sports
I never saw my whole life skeleton and
lose nah oh hey if you want to represent
the winner I know put shoveling in the
Winter Olympics right yeah find the best
shovel in the world and make the finals
head to head not against it POC head to
head to driveway side by side little
uphill some guy from Russia some guy
from Buffalo get him buddy go go
here's the thing if you win the Olympic
shoveling you don't get a gold medal you
twenty dollars is $20 toward that
driveway up you mow lawns ya tryin to
get you the Summer Games I'm gonna name
Summer Games feel great last year United
States the great gonna relay that was
fun man I think here's my thing about
the Olympics they always I love them but
they remind me of how ignorant I am like
internationally I have no clue other
countries flags I'm so bad at I I was
watching a cycling I was rooting for the
guy from the Red Cross I go come on
buddy
I told my wife I got the medic is
pulling away from everybody turns out
he's from Switzerland that's a I thought
there's gonna be the feel-good story of
the world
this guy's gonna win the race and
deliver blood it's not the way here's a
race I want to see the fastest man on
lands Usain Bolt there's no debate
fastest man to water Michael Phelps
I want to see those two racing 100
meters through a swamp
[Music]
that's why those jokes that doesn't get
50% but I like it I like it I watch
everything on TV I don't know if that
makes me a bad fan cuz you're supposed
to go support your team live but all
these new arenas and stadiums they
aren't big jumbo Tron's now that's a
whole new trend big jumbo Tron's and
that was very exciting until somebody
invented the kiss-cam
and that's where the house camera they
just sue Minter you to kiss and i scared
the hell out of me and my sister at a
Knicks game well that's us Katie you
want to piss off this crowd or going to
therapy well I want to have
[Applause]
I do a lot of travel and had an easy
trip out here nice Jeff I flew out and I
like flying I understand if people don't
but my one thing the airlines they don't
communicate bad news they never do that
I had a flight cancelled once they may
tell us they had us all we're at the
gate and they keep delaying the
departure time oh it's a finally go up
to the gate attendant I go hey what's
going on it was all flights cancelled oh
I know why he goes we're gonna have a
plane go neither do I unfortunately but
the difference I wasn't selling airfare
that's a very not to the airlines
defense they never say hey we got an
airplane but their website had a lot of
photographs of airplanes that like you
were led to believe that was a
bait-and-switch I do a lot of drivin ton
of driving I think the highways are
safer and ever because those rumble
strips boy has a good imagine between
those rumble strips and cruise control I
sleep so much better guys I've driven
across the country clap have you ever
done it yeah all the way to the coast
it's fed to me it's more exciting going
west you drive west you drive forever
you cross a time zone in your car
heading west right at that instant it's
an hour earlier oh I get so excited I
feel like I'm from the future I'll burst
into a restaurant go listen up everybody
you're not gonna believe us
I've already seen noon today
yeah I'm from the future how far in the
future in one hour
I'd like to live on a time zone that'd
be cool because a lot of times the
boundary it's a little River right you
end up with these two little towns
facing each other cause a little river
they're an hour apart if you live there
you go back and forth and time whenever
you want to watch jeopardy on one side
of the river scoot to the other side
look like a genius the biggest perk you
can eat and then go swimming immediately
how exciting what happened so I'm flying
home tomorrow be back with the team I
like being married it's good I was
single for a long time that gets tough
dating is weird I want a date with the
weirdest a was a woman who was older
than me and I knew her from high school
that was a word cuz remember high school
if you weren't the same grade it's a big
deal you know
and when we met I was a little 9th
grader and she was a cafeteria lady
our first date she cooked me dinner at
her house
sloppy joes with tater tots a yeah and I
knew she liked me when she gave me two
chocolate milks cuz you're only supposed
to buy one I actually want to go back to
my high school cafeteria I really do
just not for the food just to the
efficiency was unbelievable cuz I worked
in restaurants all my high-school Bitzer
400 kids and three minutes the key
regardless of the food they served
everything with an ice cream scooper
have your tray ready there you go what
is it hot dog what's this corn on a cone
remember to corn in high school what
even yellows like translucent gravy you
feel your corn on the floor he could
even see it anywhere where my father won
there's my cool ash I lost my corn but
the key they had a scooper for each
different food that's what sped
everything though you know he's
dedicated thing cuz that's my thing I
love ice cream I can't eat ice cream
cones I marked its places never have
enough scoopers I think you just have a
scooper for each flavor but they don't
Baskin Robbins 31 different flavors one
scooper so after every customer they
rinse off that one scooper by dunking it
in that muck bucket they go faster oh
yeah I'll pretend that was sanitary no
problem
[Applause]
yeah a little-little tadpole on top
there there's a little tablet you don't
cancel the ice cream I'm gonna gross you
out and drink the bucket hand me that
bucket [__] the turn us into Fear
Factor
[Music]
oh boy so next week I'm going to Canada
with it Canadians here you never know
okay I'll be in Montreal that's a great
city I don't know if you're there like
we hate that town we're not trying to be
always intimidating going akin I feel
like they're very much smarter than us
I've got a Montreal I've time I go to
Montreal go you know I'm gonna learn
French I'm gonna challenge myself I'm a
gates and culture right and then by day
two I'm like whatever I try to learn
that Celsius system before I do anything
else you know cuz when you go into a
country and you don't even know what the
temperature is you're feeling a
kindergartener right I was in Montreal
one time during this summer
the forecast is 19 degrees right sounds
a little nippy to an American right so I
asked a local guy go hey 90 degrees hey
wait what's that in Fahrenheit he goes
it's real easy to convert detective
Celsius multiplied by 9 divided by five
and then had 32 you know be even easier
if he gave me the answer that would be
alive I think I don't know I had a
algebra final today
I'll make it yes/no am i wearing shorts
later that's all I needed over Joe but
Canadian people very nice super friendly
very very nice even the customs people
are nice because I cross the border by
car all the time and I've been searched
in each direction turn me nerd coming
back I've had my cards coming back
they'll they take your cell phone and
they put you in his room and things like
an hour and a hat right I got search
going in a Canada one time the guy was
apologetic because I'm so sorry
because we have to search your car you
can wait inside or you can come out and
watch come watch I want to see you finer
stuff in here I'm looking for somewhere
- for packing Nutter butters man a lot
they're in here somewhere
you find him you get to
no the only time ever clown around when
the authority figure at backfired ice
back over the money hometown I saw a
police car with one headlight on I got
this it'd be funny huh I'll do a little
role reversal
the officer he'll get the joke we'll
share a big chuckle so I flagged down
his cop car run up to the window hey hey
hey you know I pulled you over
you're missing a headlight if you do
that make sure your car's registered
oh you guys are fun so uh hey I'm saving
up to go to Spain so if anyone's by
candy bars for me after the show I'm
doing my Spanish club for my head school
I was thinking back I go what was the
easiest money I ever made my whole life
well selling candy bars like Little
League junior high stuff I had a I was
hooked up man if you did that you bribed
had to go knock on doors right try to
sell on the camera then make a second
trip to deliver two candy bar maybe a
third trip to get paid not me
I put the candy bars in the fridge my
brothers would eat them all my mom would
feel bad she pay me I still haven't told
her I was eating candy bars - Shh baby
it's gonna be bars no I got a couple of
money-making ideas
I'm always thinking how can I make a
little more items at the dentist
two weeks ago my dad is first of all my
dentist I like the guy who's great guy
give you mixed messages on the other
stuff but he goes hey you need to stop
your toothbrush okay and that for 20
minutes he scrapes my teeth for metal
hooks you need softer hooks
[Music]
but here's my money-making idea I've my
front tooth is fake I got it knocked out
playing a little league win at 11 so my
whole adult life faked to it and if
anyone has fake teeth you know they
don't stain like your natural fading so
slowly they don't match right it's my
dentist trying to talk me into whitening
whitening my natural teeth
no and I'm on a budget here I don't want
to be wait cheaper to stain the fake
tooth
I got 31 teeth that look the same one is
different and if you bought a new door
for your house it didn't match you
wouldn't repaint your house and repaint
the door so here's my invention I
invented coffee strips everybody copies
dead right before you go to bed put a
coffee strip right on your fake dude
it's decaf I won't keep you up I thought
that there
that's a $200 idea right there folks max
well my dad excuse me the little dental
floss to go do you guys get hooked up
with a little dental floss to go I don't
have the heart to tell the guy yeah I
didn't finish the one from last year but
I appreciate
[Applause]
it's only three yards I still got a yard
left I use two yards a day before cuz I
know I'm gonna die but here's how here's
how I'll leave you this here's how I'm
planning to make money I'm writing
screenplays for movies and I just want
to write one big blockbuster and quit so
I'm shooting for the top I wrote a
sequel to Titanic wasn't my favorite
movie but it made two billion dollars
worldwide ago let's get on this thing
right and I don't we want to see the
same cast in the sequel and I know Jack
passed away at the end of the first one
that's okay I gave Jack an identical
twin brother played by Leonardo DiCaprio
the twin meets Kate Winslet at Jack's
funeral they fall in love and get
engaged and for the wedding they try to
go back to England but they take
Hindenburg
big money right there I wrote a sequel
to a movie I never even saw it's from
the same director James Cameron did a
movie called the abyss I never even saw
it I don't know the plot and I wrote the
sequel son of a [__] right there but
here's the new trend but movies used to
be if a movie was a big hit they do a
sequel now the movies a big hit they go
before the original and do prequels so I
wrote to pretty close to I wrote the
fifth sense the same kid from The Sixth
Sense the only smells big finale right
here here's the prequel people on a seat
because they've been doing sequels for
four decades with no exaggeration so I
wrote the backstory that explains it all
I wrote rocky zero it's rocky Balboa's
first fight this when he learns the
punches okay so the third grade one
uppercut oh he knocks out a speech
therapist how about that everybody
[Applause]